{
    "id": "27f4ab9fba2044ab8ab3e395318a8824",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She seems nice. ………………… .., I don’t really like her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Even so",
                "Even though"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. I become a millionaire, I will always be a socialist.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Even if",
                "Although"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "‘Are you interested in going to university?’ ‘Yes, I ………………’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would like",
                "would like to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I’ll try to phone you …………………… the meeting.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "during"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I woke up …………………… the night.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "during",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I couldn’t recognize him because he was dressed …………….. a dark suit.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… the bad weather, the match was cancelled.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Because",
                "Due to",
                "In spite of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I’ve been to ………………….. too many places recently.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "rather",
                "quite"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It was a …………………. unpleasant experience.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "quite",
                "rather"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He’s not ………………….. to be a soldier.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "tall enough",
                "enough tall"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}